Mohamed Moanis Abdellatif Ali

Software Engineer

Via Carducci 7, 39100 Bolzano, Italy.

mohamed_moanis@outlook.com



+39 349 136 5301



mohamed-moanis

SUMMARY

I am a software engineer with 2 years of experience. I am a pragmatic developer who can figure his way around, work independently and get the work done. I love to automate things that I do and to generate new ideas to improve the process, the team and the product.

EDUCATION

Free University of Bozen-Bolzano - MSc Software Engineering

Oct 2018 - Oct 2020

• 2 years Erasmus Mundus Masters in Software Engineering. Full Erasmus scholarship holder.

Cairo University - BSc Electrical Engineering

Oct 2011 - July 2016

• 5 years engineering program majored in communication and computer Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Mentor Graphics - Software Development Engineer

Sep 2016 - Sep 2018

C++ / Linux

Mentor Graphics - Intern

Feb 2016 - Sep 2016

C++ / Linux

AvidBeam - Thesis Work Intern

Mar 2016 - June 2016

• C++ / ffmpeq / OpenCV / MongoDB / Ruby-on-Rails / BackboneJS / NodeJS / Ubuntu / MacOS

AvidBeam - Intern

June 2015 - Sep 2015

• C++ / ffmpeg / OpenCL / OpenCV / C# / Windows